{
    "id": "6eb3742328424a0dab96209e980f90b2",
    "title": "Easily confused words",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "afdcedbff2384a02bad38ba00ac0601b",
            "title": "Easily Confused Words",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Cold weather ............................... my health.",
                    "description": "Affect is the verb. Effect is the noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "affected",
                        "effected"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ..................................... her on her good looks.",
                    "description": "To compliment is to praise. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "complimented",
                        "complemented"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The salad perfectly ......................................... the main course.",
                    "description": "To complement is to complete.",
                    "answers": [
                        "complimented",
                        "complemented"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is not very ..................................... so don't share your secrets with her.",
                    "description": "Discreet means careful and prudent. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "discreet",
                        "discrete",
                        "discreat"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is an ........................................ scientist.",
                    "description": "Eminent means accomplished. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "eminent",
                        "imminent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "War is .........................................",
                    "description": "If something is imminent it is about to happen.",
                    "answers": [
                        "eminent",
                        "imminent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "All credit cards are .......................................... here.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "expected",
                        "accepted",
                        "excepted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The councilor was accused of ..................................... the funds.",
                    "description": "To misuse is to use something in the wrong way.",
                    "answers": [
                        "disusing",
                        "abusing",
                        "misusing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The exhibition was held in a ..................................... warehouse.",
                    "description": "Disused means no longer being used.",
                    "answers": [
                        "misused",
                        "disused",
                        "abused"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The book is so boring that it is .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "illegible",
                        "unreadable"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The prices of essential commodities ......................................... sharply.",
                    "description": "Raise is transitive. That means it must have an expressed object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "have risen",
                        "have raised"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The long journey was …………………………………...",
                    "description": "Exhausting means tiring. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "exhausting",
                        "exhaustive",
                        "exhausted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}